khanapakana.com 2014-06-29

# Direct Advert Media, LLC Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**  
KhanaPakana.com or the parent company Direct Advert Media LLC respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains what information we collect through KhanaPakana.Com (the “Website”) and when you contact us for support, how we use that information, and what choices you have.

KhanaPakana.Com may contain links to other web sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of any company or individual that KhanaPakana.Com does not control, or any web sites that you link to from the KhanaPakana.Com. You should carefully review the privacy policies of any web sites that you visit from ours to learn more about their information and privacy practices. The collection and use of your personal information shall be governed by such other party or site's privacy policy. KhanaPakana.Com is not responsible for their privacy practices.

Please take a few moments to read this Privacy Statement. By accessing KhanaPakana.Com, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement and are aware that our policies may change in the future.

**What information we collect**  
In various places on KhanaPakana.Com, we collect "Personally Identifiable Information" such as your name, screen name, location, mailing address, telephone number, email address, or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you. For example, we collect this information when you create an account, register for KP community, sign up for our email newsletter, and purchase from KhanaPakana.Com, enter a sweepstakes, contest or participate in surveys, promotions and give-away. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

We also collect "Anonymous Information" such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on KhanaPakana.Com that you visit, the search terms that you enter or the advertisements that you click. Anonymous information can and will NOT be associated with Personally Identifiable Information.

Like many Internet sites, we also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit KhanaPakana.Com the cookie identifies your computer to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We also use cookies to measure the traffic to and usage of our site and its different services and features, and other miscellaneous uses.

We also collect the personal information of third parties that is provided by visitors who submit that personal data through our Sites, in connection with, for example, referrals.

KhanaPakana.Com captures usage information as part of normal functioning. The collected information includes the specific identifiers of videos played, duration played, various quality measures, error logs, software version numbers, and other usage statistics.

The information collected from many users is aggregated for analysis and, in some instances, made generally available anonymously to KhanaPakana.Com or the parent company Direct Advert Media LLC partners and affiliates. For example, KhanaPakana.Com may use such information to provide features such as lists of popular videos, recipes, posts. KhanaPakana.Com may also use personally identifiable information to make content recommendations to individual users.

If you do not wish KhanaPakana.Com to use your information as described in this section, please follow the procedure in "What Choices You Have" below.

We do not intend that children will use KhanaPakana.Com. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 18 years of age, nor will we accept registration from them.

**How we use the information we collect  
**We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provided us to perform the services for which the data was collected, such as for user technical support and marketing activities, such as e-mail newsletters and sending you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Statement, we provide you with more information on how to opt-out of marketing communications.

We use non-Personally Identifiable Information to determine how people use KhanaPakana.Com and its services and to analyze usage and performance. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which content are accessed most frequently, and which areas of our site are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve KhanaPakana.Com.

**How we share information**  
We sometimes use third parties to help with certain aspects of our operations, such as providing marketing assistance. When we supply Personally Identifiable Information to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are contracted to perform.

We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and exchange it with advertisers and others who are interested in our services.

We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information as required by law, or if in our judgment it is necessary to protect KhanaPakana.Com or our users from loss or liability. We may share some or all of your personal information with our current or future "affiliates" (which means a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control), in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this privacy policy. If we merge with or are acquired by another company, the resulting combined company will use the information you have provided as described in this policy. If we cease operation, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services. While we cannot predict about such an unlikely event, we would hope this could provide you continuity of service.

**What choices you have  
**If you do not want to receive information about our products and services or do not want to receive information from our partners and others about products and services that might interest you, you can send an email to KhanaPakana.Com at [privacy@khanapakana.com](mailto:privacy@khanapakana.com). This e-mail address is being protected from spambots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it. We will keep track of your decision in our database. Even if you choose not to receive information from us, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important relating to our products or services.

**Postings**  
If you register to use KP Community forum, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. Your profile will also be available to other users.

**Security**  
During sessions in which greater security is required, we encrypt your transmissions using SSL ("Secure Sockets Layer"), and other security technology. This guards against the interception of the information while it is on the Internet. We keep the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, and only our employees and agents with a need to know the information are given access. However, there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. Third parties may unlawfully access transmissions or private communications. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the Sites.

**Questions  
**If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or our policies, please contact KhanaPakana.Com 

 ** _[privacy@khanapakana.com](mailto:privacy@khanapakana.com)._**
